<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="de.ovgu.cide_old"
      label="CIDE (Old Java Version)"
      version="1.2.1.qualifier"
      provider-name="Christian Kaestner / University of Magdeburg">

   <description url="http://www.fosd.de/cide">
      Old version of CIDE, no longer maintained. However this version supports some features like type-checking or export to AHEAD which have not been migrated to the new version. Do not use old and new version at the same time.

Do not install the old and the new CIDE versions in the same Eclipse installation. This feature is automatically deactivated if a newer release of CIDE is found.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2006-2008, Christian Kästner, University of Magdeburg, Germany
All rights reserved.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      CIDE is provided as a research prototype as is. Source code can
be requested for research purposes by email.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&quot;AS IS&quot; AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT
NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT
SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT,
INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES
(INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS
OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION)
HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT,
STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)
ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED
OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="CIDE Update Site" url="http://wwwiti.cs.uni-magdeburg.de/iti_db/research/cide/update/"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jface.text"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.workbench.texteditor"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.core.resources"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.core"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.jdt.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.junit4"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="coloride"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
